{
    "subject": "Abel_Gance",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Au_Secours!",
    "human_readable": "Abel Gance directed the film Au Secours!",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8526051640510559,
            "question": "Who directed the film Au Secours!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7867559790611267,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Abel Gance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6680861711502075,
            "question": "Are there any other notable films directed by Abel Gance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6240370273590088,
            "question": "What year was the film Au Secours! released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5756294131278992,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in films directed by Abel Gance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5020055770874023,
            "question": "Is Au Secours! a fictional or non-fictional film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4770982265472412,
            "question": "In what genre is the film Au Secours!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4509865641593933,
            "question": "What are some critical reviews of the film Au Secours!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3734956383705139,
            "question": "How does Au Secours! compare to other films of its era?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3586905300617218,
            "question": "What is the significance of Abel Gance's work in film history?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Abel Gance directed the film Au Secours!",
            "html": "yago_4153_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does Au Secours! compare to other films of its era?",
            "html": "yago_4153_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some critical reviews of the film Au Secours!",
            "html": "yago_4153_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what genre is the film Au Secours!",
            "html": "yago_4153_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4153_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4153_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4153_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4153_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4153_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4153_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4153_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4153_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4153_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4153_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple \"Abel Gance directed the film Au Secours!\":\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\n\n* In file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_4153/re-ranker-msmarco/13.txt, it is mentioned that \"As we mark the centenary of \u201cAu Secours!\u201c, this silent comedy not only stands as a testament to the brilliance of Max Linder but also serves as a poignant reminder of his enduring legacy.  Directed by Abel Gance...\"\n* This indicates that Abel Gance was indeed the director of the film Au Secours!."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe document states, \"Directed by Abel Gance, this film showcases Linder's comedic genius and his unparalleled ability to captivate audiences with his charm and wit.\" This sentence confirms that Abel Gance directed the film \"Au Secours!\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}